Guide to the Robert Fitch Papers WAG.261
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Subject Files
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Local 638: Annual Report (Form 5500), 2001 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Local 638: Gambino Case, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): National Museum of Catholic Art and History, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): New York, 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Pension Fund: Exemption, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Real Estate Corruption, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Tommy L. Preuitt, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): UA Journal, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - United Auto Workers (UAW), 2000-2004 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - United Auto Workers (UAW): Corruption, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - United Auto Workers (UAW): Corruption, 2000-2005 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - United Auto Workers (UAW): Corruption, 2000-2005 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - United Auto Workers (UAW): Two Tier Wages, 2000-2005 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC), 1982-1998 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC), 1994-2000 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC), 1995-2002 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC), 1996-2004 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC), 1998-2002 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC): Ambassador Resort (Florida), 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC): Corruption, 1992-2004 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC): Detroit, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC): Douglas J. McCarron, 1998-2002 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC): Hiring Halls, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC): Kenneth Conboy, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC): Lucchese Construction Group Indictment, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC): Mike Billelo: Interview, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC): Richard Blum, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC): Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive Materials, 1990, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC): Ted Casselman, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - United Domestic Workers of America, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW), 1997-2001 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 2004 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): California: Grocery Strike, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): California: Grocery Strike: Assessments, 2001-2004 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): California: Grocery Strike: Divisiveness, 1996-2004 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): California: Grocery Strike: Support, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): California: Grocery Strike: Teamsters, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): California: Strike, 1985-1990 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Canada, 2001-2004 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Corruption, 1971-2004 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Dominick's, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Guild for Professional Pharmacists, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Grupo Gigante, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Hugh Finnamore (Workplace Strategies, Inc), 1989-2004 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): International Longshore and Warehouse Union (ILWU), 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Jack Loveall, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): James Ridgway de Szigethy, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Kroger Grocery Stores, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Leadership (Joe Hansen, Douglas Dority, William Wynn), 1993-2004 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Local 56: Bankruptcy, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Ray Rogers (organizer), 1986 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Salaries, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): St. Louis: Strike, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Textile Processors Battle, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW): Tyson Foods, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - United Public Workers Union (UPW): Gary Rodrigues, 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - United States Department of Labor: Press Releases, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Usman dan Fodio, undated (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Venice, Florida, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Series II: Writings
  Contains drafts and copies Fitch's writings, which were published in periodicals and journals including The Village Voice, The Baffler, Newsday and The Nation. For many of his published articles, multiple versions are present, many with annotatations and proposed revisions by Jane LaTour and Martin Fishgold. Multiple drafts of Fitch's 2006 book Solidarity for Sale, including early versions under the title of Sellout!, are included in this series.
  - About the Author, undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Anatomy of a Mob Run Union, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - The Asian Bear Arrives in the U.S., Aug 1998 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - The Assassination of New York: Reviews, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Bad Faith and the Common Good, Nov 2006 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Beyond "Charlie Brown", Feb 2010 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - The Big Fix, Sep 1999 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Big Labor's Big Secret, Dec 2005 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Black Jobs, White Theories, undated (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Card Check: Labor's Charlie Brown Moment?, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - The Carpenter's Greatest Hits, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - The Carpenter's Greatest Hits: Jane Latour Edits, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - The Case of the Disappearing Work, Dec 1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Circling La Guardia, Nov 1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - The Coming Breakup of New York, Apr 1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Crash, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Dancing with Wolves: Social Movements or Social Control?, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - DC37 Crashes, Nov 1998 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - DC37 Epilog, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Dead Men Leading, Apr 1996 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Division of Labor, Dec 1996 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Downsizing Fills Up, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - The Dutch Masters, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Economic Suicide, Nov 1993 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - The Empire Strikes Back, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Explaining New York City's Aberrant Economy, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - The Fashion Fascists, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - The Fat Cats of Labor, Oct 1995 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Fighting Back, Jan 2000 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Flubber, Dec 1997 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Foundations and the Charter, Dec 1989 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Foundations and the Charter: Responses, Feb 1990 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - From Jobs to Hugs, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - A Global Crisis Made in the U.S.A., Nov 1997 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Greedy Gus, Jan 1996 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - H. Ross Perot: America's First Welfare Billionaire, Nov 1971 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Hard Hat News, 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - The Haunting of Hill House, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Have You Seen the Mother Jones Makeover?, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Heartbreak Highway, undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - How DC37 Caught Vote Fraud Fever, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - How Perot Made a Quarter Billion Dollars by Running for President, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - How Stanley Got His Hammer, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - How to Fix DC37, 1999, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Imperialism: The Coming Period, undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - In Bologna, Small is Beautiful, May 1996 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - In Defense of Washington and Wall Street, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - It Wasn't Management That Killed Labor, undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Just What the City Doesn't Need, Oct 2001 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Labor Pain, Nov 1996 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - The Laborers, undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - The Labor's Two Worlds, Nov 1995 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Local 138: A Case Study in the Roach Motel Effect, undated (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Local 138: The Revolution Betrayed, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Lombardo's Legacy, undated (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Look Behind the Union Label, undated (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Looting Labor's Capital, undated (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - The Man Who Destroyed Honcho Heaven, undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Mayor, The Sequel, Jul 1990 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous drafts, 2004; 727 kilobytes (8 computer files) (E-records 1)
    Interview with Fitch, notes and drafts of Learning to Labor on High Steel, Philadelphia '69, Did the Democrats Do-In Ron Carey, Unite's Garment Gulag, What's Wrong With Corruption?
    Access Restrictions
    Advanced notice required for access.
  - A More Perfect Union?, Jul 2005 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Mr. Wallerstein's Planet, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Nelson Rockefeller: An Anti-Obituary, Jul 1979 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - The New Poor Laws, Jan 1995 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - The New Worker Atop, Feb 1993 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - New York Budget War, May 1995 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - New York City: What a Friend We Have in David, Apr 1991 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - New York Forum Column, 1988-1991 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - New York's Real Transit Crisis, Jan 2006 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Nixon: With a Little Help For His Friends, Mar 1970 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Of Urban Bondage, Apr 1991 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Office Buildings - As Obsolete as Walk Ups, Nov 1993 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - OPEC: The Big Cartel That Couldn't, undated (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Our Cash Crop: Office Towers, Jun 1988 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Our Labor Leaders Need French Lessons, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - The Political Economy of New York City, undated (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Prisoners of Money, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - The Producers, undated (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Prolog to Reform, undated (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Remembering Jerry Rubin, Apr 1995 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Rent Control Reform, undated (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - The Return of the Shadow, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Revolution in the Teamsters, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Raod to Rudy, Nov 1993 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - SEIU: From Mobsters to Managers, undated (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Sellout! How Corruption Beat Reform in the Battle to Revive America's Unions, 1998, undated (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Sellout! How Corruption Beat Reform in the Battle to Revive America's Unions, undated (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Sewing Suspicion, Apr 1998 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Sleeping With the Enemy, Nov 1997 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Solidarity for Sale
  - Solidarity for Sale: Chapter 1, undated (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Chapter 2, undated (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Chapter 3, undated (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Chapter 4-6, undated (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Chapter 8, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Chapter 8, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Chapter 8, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Chapter 9, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Chapter 10, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Chapter 11, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Chapter 13, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Conclusion, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Drafts (complete), undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Public Affairs (publisher), 1999-2006 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Solidarity for Sale: Reviews, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Stardust Memories, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - State/Local Fiscal Crises, Oct 1990 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Sweeney: American Needs a Raise`, Nov 1996 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Sweeney Among the Warlords, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Talk Show Proposal, Mar 1998 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - The Two Labor Demos, Jul 1998 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - The Two Souls of Rudolph Giuliani, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Uncreative Destruction, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Underexposure, Oct 2000 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Union For Sale, Sep 1998 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - The Union From Hell, Jan 1998 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - The Union From Hell: Responses, May 1998 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Union Jacked, Aug 1999 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - The Union Makes Us Strong?, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Union Reformation, Apr 2000 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Unkindest Cuts, Feb 1995 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Urban Origins of the Great Repression, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Vetting God's Politics, Nov 2006 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - What's Left to Write?, May 1989 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Who Rules the Corporations?, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - White House, DNC and Clinton-Gore Campaign Fundraising Efforts, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Who Is Ross Perot?, Jun 1992 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Who's Who on the Far Left?, Nov 1996 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Why American Workers Need Constitutional Protection, May 2008 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Why Johnny Can't Organize, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Series III: Speeches
  Contains copies of Fitch's speeches and talks delivered in a variety of venues around the country, mostly on the topic of labor union corruption. Multiple versions of speeches are often present, and in some cases, research material associated with a speech is included. Flyers promoting events at which Fitch spoke are also present in this series.
  - Beyond Obama and McCain, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Can Rent Control Last?, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Change They Believe In, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - City Unions, undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Creeping Quango's, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Digital Delusions, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Ethical Culture Society Discussion of Solidarity for Sale, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Flyers, 1993-2007 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Hell's Kitchen, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - If I Had a Hammer, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - In Defense of Washington and Wall Street, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Irrelevant Moderns and Relevant Victorians, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Labor History Month, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Labor Left and Union Democracy, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Labor's Voices Panel, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Life of Brian, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Municipal Incoherence, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Organized Labor's Five Pillars of Corruption, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Power and Property, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - The Question of Corruption, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Reinventing the Sweatshop, undated (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Teamsters, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Their Morals and Ours, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Third Regional Plan, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - UNITE: Still Fighting for Lower Wages, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - What Should New York Jews Do?, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - What's Wrong With Radical Economics?, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Why American Workers Need Constitutional Protection, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 64)
- Series IV: Personal Material
  Contains a small amount of Fitch's personal material, including clippings, interviews, correspondence, certificates, diplomas, an undated curriculum vitae and photographs. Tributes and remarks made at his memorial service are also included in this series, as are materials from Fitch's mother Jo, including a children's books, Barnabus the Hippopotamus, that she created.
  - Adoption, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Birth and Name Change Certificates, 1938, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1986-2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2006-2010, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Public Affairs (Solidarity for Sale), 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Curriculum Vitae, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Interviews, 1996-2006 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Jo Fitch (mother): Correspondence, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Jo Fitch (mother): Barnabus the Hippopotamus, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Memorial Remarks, Sep 18, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, 1991, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: SEIU Local 32BJ, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Profiles, 1999-2010 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - State University of New York at Binghamton: Diploma and Transcript, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Tributes, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Series V: Cassette Tapes and Floppy Disks
  Contains cassette tapes with copies of Crossing Wall Street, Fitch's show on WBAI-FM, as well as interviews with rank and file labor union members. The cassettes containing interviews appear to be copies of interviews conducted by Jane LaTour in her capacity as archivist of the Burton Hall Papers, and are available at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives in the Burton Hall Union Democracy Oral History Project (OH 34). Two unlabeled 3.5 inch floppy disks are also part of this series.
  Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
  Access [DVDs/ CDs / terminal] for audiovisual materials in the collection are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
  - Crossing Wall Street (WBAI-FM show), Jul 6, 1998 (Box 19)
  - Crossing Wall Street (WBAI-FM show), Aug 24, 1998 (Box 19)
  - Crossing Wall Street (WBAI-FM show), Aug 31, 1998 (Box 19)
  - Crossing Wall Street (WBAI-FM show), Sep 7, 1998 (Box 19)
  - Crossing Wall Street (WBAI-FM show), undated (Box 19)
  - Floppy Disks: Two Unmarked 3.5 inch Floppy Disks, undated (Box 19)
  - Interviews: Charles Curd (International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 282), Apr 29, 1995 (Box 19)
  - Interviews: Charles Ensley, Apr 29, 1995 (Box 19)
  - Interviews: Larry Kudla/J. Carter (Tape 1 of 2), Nov 4, 1993 (Box 19)
  - Interviews: Larry Kudla/J. Carter (Tape 2 of 2), Nov 4, 1993 (Box 19)
  - Interviews: Leon Olson, Apr 29, 1995 (Box 19)
  - Interviews: Unidentified Interview, undated (Box 19)
  - Interviews: Unidentified Interview, undated (Box 19)
  - Interviews: Unidentified Interview, undated (Box 19)
- Series VI. 2015 Accretion
  This accretion features published and unpublished administrative documents from the files of Robert Fitch of both a personal and professional nature. The accretion includes emails, articles, and course files including notes, articles and syllabi for Fitch's college courses as well as reseach, notes, and original writings pertaining to his books. The series also includes materials concerning finances, union corruption, and consultations on New York City for Arthur Cheliotes.
  Arrangement
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2630 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2630 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
  - File List (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Emails (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Speech (Part 1) [# -J] (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
  - Speech (Part 2) [K-U] (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
  - Speaking Opportunities (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - New Articles Part II (G-W) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - New Articles Part I (Subfolders, A-F) (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Card Check Part 1 [1 proofs.rtfd - Charlie] (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Articles (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
  - Adjuncts (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Const. Ammend#6F14 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Laborers (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Hardhat (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Work/ Dissertation-BF (Box 20, Folder 17 - 18)
  - Emails (Part 2) (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Bio (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Fax (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - ASONY (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Blog (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Anthology/Collected Works (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Finance/Proofs.rtfd/Goldner reply.rtfd (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Fire Power (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - George (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - New York Bk (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Finance Part II( (o-w) (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Goldman.Sachs (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Bubble (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Crash Book (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Finance (Part I) (B-C) (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Finance Book (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Finance (Part II) (D-N) (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Dollars and Dems (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Obama Book (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Chicago Chapter (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Politics Course (Part 1) ["Power" - J] (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Recommendations (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Welfare (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - World Politics (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Intro Sociology (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - MET (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Union Course (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Revolution Course (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Queens (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - New York Course (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Politics Course (Part III) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Cities Course (Box 21, Folder 7)